(Stuart:)Must be nice.
(Stuart:)Nobody wants anything
that comes out of me.
- I wonder what he's doing this very second.
- Conducting experiments in zero gravity.
(Raj:)Peering through his telescope
at the birth of the cosmos.
(Sheldon:)Whatever it is,
we know his life will never be the same.
(Mrs Wolowitz(off):)Howard, can you hear me?
I can hear you without the phone!
(Mrs Wolowitz(off):)Don't be snippy.
I'm just excited to talk to my baby.
(Howard:)I'm excited to talk to you too.
(Mrs Wolowitz(off):)So, what's this mishegas about you
moving out to go live with the little Polish girl?
How about calling her my wife? Heh.
(Mrs Wolowitz(off):)Wives don't take boys from their mothers.
(Howard:)They do, that's why we marry them.
(Mrs Wolowitz(off):)I just hope I'm not dead
from a broken heart before you get back.
(Howard:)Ma, please, everyone from NASA
is listening to this phone call.
(Mrs Wolowitz(off):)Good, they should know
what a horrible son you are.
(Howard:)Okay, Ma, great talking to you.
Gotta go.
(Howard:)Well...
(Howard:)...space is ruined.